[
	{
		"question":"Fähigkeit",
		"answer":"ability"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zugriff",
		"answer":"access"
	},
	{
		"question":"Unfall",
		"answer":"accident"
	},
	{
		"question":"Konto",
		"answer":"account"
	},
	{
		"question":"Handlung",
		"answer":"act"
	},
	{
		"question":"Aktion",
		"answer":"action"
	},
	{
		"question":"Aktivität",
		"answer":"activity"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schauspieler",
		"answer":"actor"
	},
	{
		"question":"Anzeige",
		"answer":"ad"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ergänzung",
		"answer":"addition"
	},
	{
		"question":"Adresse",
		"answer":"address"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verwaltung",
		"answer":"administration"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vorteil",
		"answer":"advantage"
	},
	{
		"question":"Werbung",
		"answer":"advertising"
	},
	{
		"question":"Beratung",
		"answer":"advice"
	},
	{
		"question":"Affäre",
		"answer":"affair"
	},
	{
		"question":"Alter",
		"answer":"age"
	},
	{
		"question":"Agentur",
		"answer":"agency"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vereinbarung",
		"answer":"agreement"
	},
	{
		"question":"Luft",
		"answer":"air"
	},
	{
		"question":"Flughafen",
		"answer":"airport"
	},
	{
		"question":"Alkohol",
		"answer":"alcohol"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ehrgeiz",
		"answer":"ambition"
	},
	{
		"question":"Menge",
		"answer":"amount"
	},
	{
		"question":"Analyse",
		"answer":"analysis"
	},
	{
		"question":"Analytiker",
		"answer":"analyst"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tier",
		"answer":"animal"
	},
	{
		"question":"Antwort",
		"answer":"answer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Angst",
		"answer":"anxiety"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wohnung",
		"answer":"apartment"
	},
	{
		"question":"Aussehen",
		"answer":"appearance"
	},
	{
		"question":"Apfel",
		"answer":"apple"
	},
	{
		"question":"Anwendung",
		"answer":"application"
	},
	{
		"question":"Termin",
		"answer":"appointment"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bereich",
		"answer":"area"
	},
	{
		"question":"Streit",
		"answer":"argument"
	},
	{
		"question":"Armee",
		"answer":"army"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ankunft",
		"answer":"arrival"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kunst",
		"answer":"art"
	},
	{
		"question":"Artikel",
		"answer":"article"
	},
	{
		"question":"Aspekt",
		"answer":"aspect"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zuordnung",
		"answer":"assignment"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hilfe",
		"answer":"assistance"
	},
	{
		"question":"Assistent",
		"answer":"assistant"
	},
	{
		"question":"Assoziation",
		"answer":"association"
	},
	{
		"question":"Annahme",
		"answer":"assumption"
	},
	{
		"question":"Atmosphäre",
		"answer":"atmosphere"
	},
	{
		"question":"Versuch",
		"answer":"attempt"
	},
	{
		"question":"Aufmerksamkeit",
		"answer":"attention"
	},
	{
		"question":"Haltung",
		"answer":"attitude"
	},
	{
		"question":"Publikum",
		"answer":"audience"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tante",
		"answer":"aunt"
	},
	{
		"question":"Durchschnitt",
		"answer":"average"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bewusstsein",
		"answer":"awareness"
	},
	{
		"question":"Rücken",
		"answer":"back"
	},
	{
		"question":"schlechte",
		"answer":"bad"
	},
	{
		"question":"Balance",
		"answer":"balance"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ball",
		"answer":"ball"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bank",
		"answer":"bank"
	},
	{
		"question":"Baseball",
		"answer":"baseball"
	},
	{
		"question":"Basis",
		"answer":"basis"
	},
	{
		"question":"Korb",
		"answer":"basket"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bad",
		"answer":"bath"
	},
	{
		"question":"Badezimmer",
		"answer":"bathroom"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schlafzimmer",
		"answer":"bedroom"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bier",
		"answer":"beer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Anfang",
		"answer":"beginning"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vorteil",
		"answer":"benefit"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vogel",
		"answer":"bird"
	},
	{
		"question":"Geburt",
		"answer":"birth"
	},
	{
		"question":"Geburtstag",
		"answer":"birthday"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bit",
		"answer":"bit"
	},
	{
		"question":"Blut",
		"answer":"blood"
	},
	{
		"question":"Brett",
		"answer":"board"
	},
	{
		"question":"Boot",
		"answer":"boat"
	},
	{
		"question":"Körper",
		"answer":"body"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bonus",
		"answer":"bonus"
	},
	{
		"question":"Buch",
		"answer":"book"
	},
	{
		"question":"Chef",
		"answer":"boss"
	},
	{
		"question":"Boden",
		"answer":"bottom"
	},
	{
		"question":"Box",
		"answer":"box"
	},
	{
		"question":"Junge",
		"answer":"boy"
	},
	{
		"question":"Freund",
		"answer":"boyfriend"
	},
	{
		"question":"Brot",
		"answer":"bread"
	},
	{
		"question":"Atem",
		"answer":"breath"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bruder",
		"answer":"brother"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gebäude",
		"answer":"building"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bus",
		"answer":"bus"
	},
	{
		"question":"Geschäft",
		"answer":"business"
	},
	{
		"question":"Käufer",
		"answer":"buyer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schrank",
		"answer":"cabinet"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kamera",
		"answer":"camera"
	},
	{
		"question":"Krebs",
		"answer":"cancer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kandidat",
		"answer":"candidate"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kapital",
		"answer":"capital"
	},
	{
		"question":"Auto",
		"answer":"car"
	},
	{
		"question":"Karte",
		"answer":"card"
	},
	{
		"question":"Pflege",
		"answer":"care"
	},
	{
		"question":"Karriere",
		"answer":"career"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fall",
		"answer":"case"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bargeld",
		"answer":"cash"
	},
	{
		"question":"Katze",
		"answer":"cat"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kategorie",
		"answer":"category"
	},
	{
		"question":"Anlass",
		"answer":"cause"
	},
	{
		"question":"Feier",
		"answer":"celebration"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zelle",
		"answer":"cell"
	},
	{
		"question":"Meisterschaft",
		"answer":"championship"
	},
	{
		"question":"Chance",
		"answer":"chance"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kapitel",
		"answer":"chapter"
	},
	{
		"question":"Nächstenliebe",
		"answer":"charity"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wange",
		"answer":"cheek"
	},
	{
		"question":"Chemie",
		"answer":"chemistry"
	},
	{
		"question":"Brust",
		"answer":"chest"
	},
	{
		"question":"Huhn",
		"answer":"chicken"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kind",
		"answer":"child"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kindheit",
		"answer":"childhood"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schokolade",
		"answer":"chocolate"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wahl",
		"answer":"choice"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kirche",
		"answer":"church"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zigarette",
		"answer":"cigarette"
	},
	{
		"question":"Stadt",
		"answer":"city"
	},
	{
		"question":"Klasse",
		"answer":"class"
	},
	{
		"question":"Klassenzimmer",
		"answer":"classroom"
	},
	{
		"question":"Klient",
		"answer":"client"
	},
	{
		"question":"Klima",
		"answer":"climate"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kleidung",
		"answer":"clothes"
	},
	{
		"question":"Küste",
		"answer":"coast"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kaffee",
		"answer":"coffee"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sammlung",
		"answer":"collection"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hochschule",
		"answer":"college"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kombination",
		"answer":"combination"
	},
	{
		"question":"Komitee",
		"answer":"committee"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kommunikation",
		"answer":"communication"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gemeinschaft",
		"answer":"community"
	},
	{
		"question":"Unternehmen",
		"answer":"company"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vergleich",
		"answer":"comparison"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wettbewerb",
		"answer":"competition"
	},
	{
		"question":"Beschwerde",
		"answer":"complaint"
	},
	{
		"question":"Computer",
		"answer":"computer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Konzept",
		"answer":"concept"
	},
	{
		"question":"Abschluss",
		"answer":"conclusion"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bedingung",
		"answer":"condition"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verwirrung",
		"answer":"confusion"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verbindung",
		"answer":"connection"
	},
	{
		"question":"Konsequenz",
		"answer":"consequence"
	},
	{
		"question":"Konstruktion",
		"answer":"construction"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kontakt",
		"answer":"contact"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kontext",
		"answer":"context"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vertrag",
		"answer":"contract"
	},
	{
		"question":"Beitrag",
		"answer":"contribution"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kontrolle",
		"answer":"control"
	},
	{
		"question":"Konversation",
		"answer":"conversation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Cookie",
		"answer":"cookie"
	},
	{
		"question":"Land",
		"answer":"country"
	},
	{
		"question":"Landkreis",
		"answer":"county"
	},
	{
		"question":"Mut",
		"answer":"courage"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kurs",
		"answer":"course"
	},
	{
		"question":"Cousin",
		"answer":"cousin"
	},
	{
		"question":"Handwerk",
		"answer":"craft"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kredit",
		"answer":"credit"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kritik",
		"answer":"criticism"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kultur",
		"answer":"culture"
	},
	{
		"question":"Währung",
		"answer":"currency"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kunde",
		"answer":"customer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zyklus",
		"answer":"cycle"
	},
	{
		"question":"Papa",
		"answer":"dad"
	},
	{
		"question":"Daten",
		"answer":"data"
	},
	{
		"question":"Datenbank",
		"answer":"database"
	},
	{
		"question":"Datum",
		"answer":"date"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tag",
		"answer":"day"
	},
	{
		"question":"Händler",
		"answer":"dealer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tod",
		"answer":"death"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schulden",
		"answer":"debt"
	},
	{
		"question":"Entscheidung",
		"answer":"decision"
	},
	{
		"question":"Definition",
		"answer":"definition"
	},
	{
		"question":"Lieferung",
		"answer":"delivery"
	},
	{
		"question":"Nachfrage",
		"answer":"demand"
	},
	{
		"question":"Abteilung",
		"answer":"department"
	},
	{
		"question":"Abreise",
		"answer":"departure"
	},
	{
		"question":"Depression",
		"answer":"depression"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tiefe",
		"answer":"depth"
	},
	{
		"question":"Beschreibung",
		"answer":"description"
	},
	{
		"question":"Design",
		"answer":"design"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schreibtisch",
		"answer":"desk"
	},
	{
		"question":"Entwicklung",
		"answer":"development"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gerät",
		"answer":"device"
	},
	{
		"question":"Diamant",
		"answer":"diamond"
	},
	{
		"question":"Unterschied",
		"answer":"difference"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schwierigkeit",
		"answer":"difficulty"
	},
	{
		"question":"Abendessen",
		"answer":"dinner"
	},
	{
		"question":"Richtung",
		"answer":"direction"
	},
	{
		"question":"Regisseur",
		"answer":"director"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schmutz",
		"answer":"dirt"
	},
	{
		"question":"Katastrophe",
		"answer":"disaster"
	},
	{
		"question":"Disziplin",
		"answer":"discipline"
	},
	{
		"question":"Diskussion",
		"answer":"discussion"
	},
	{
		"question":"Krankheit",
		"answer":"disease"
	},
	{
		"question":"Scheibe",
		"answer":"disk"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verteilung",
		"answer":"distribution"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hund",
		"answer":"dog"
	},
	{
		"question":"Drama",
		"answer":"drama"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schublade",
		"answer":"drawer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zeichnung",
		"answer":"drawing"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fahrer",
		"answer":"driver"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ohr",
		"answer":"ear"
	},
	{
		"question":"Erde",
		"answer":"earth"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wirtschaft",
		"answer":"economics"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wirtschaft",
		"answer":"economy"
	},
	{
		"question":"Redakteur",
		"answer":"editor"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bildung",
		"answer":"education"
	},
	{
		"question":"Effekt",
		"answer":"effect"
	},
	{
		"question":"Effizienz",
		"answer":"efficiency"
	},
	{
		"question":"Anstrengung",
		"answer":"effort"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ei",
		"answer":"egg"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wahl",
		"answer":"election"
	},
	{
		"question":"Aufzug",
		"answer":"elevator"
	},
	{
		"question":"Emotion",
		"answer":"emotion"
	},
	{
		"question":"Betonung",
		"answer":"emphasis"
	},
	{
		"question":"Mitarbeiter",
		"answer":"employee"
	},
	{
		"question":"Arbeitgeber",
		"answer":"employer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Beschäftigung",
		"answer":"employment"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ende",
		"answer":"end"
	},
	{
		"question":"Energie",
		"answer":"energy"
	},
	{
		"question":"Motor",
		"answer":"engine"
	},
	{
		"question":"Unterhaltung",
		"answer":"entertainment"
	},
	{
		"question":"Begeisterung",
		"answer":"enthusiasm"
	},
	{
		"question":"Eintrag",
		"answer":"entry"
	},
	{
		"question":"Umwelt",
		"answer":"environment"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ausrüstung",
		"answer":"equipment"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fehler",
		"answer":"error"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gründung",
		"answer":"establishment"
	},
	{
		"question":"Anwesen",
		"answer":"estate"
	},
	{
		"question":"Veranstaltung",
		"answer":"event"
	},
	{
		"question":"Prüfung",
		"answer":"exam"
	},
	{
		"question":"Beispiel",
		"answer":"example"
	},
	{
		"question":"Austausch",
		"answer":"exchange"
	},
	{
		"question":"Aufregung",
		"answer":"excitement"
	},
	{
		"question":"Übung",
		"answer":"exercise"
	},
	{
		"question":"Erfahrung",
		"answer":"experience"
	},
	{
		"question":"Erklärung",
		"answer":"explanation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ausdruck",
		"answer":"expression"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ausmaß",
		"answer":"extent"
	},
	{
		"question":"Auge",
		"answer":"eye"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gesicht",
		"answer":"face"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tatsache",
		"answer":"fact"
	},
	{
		"question":"Misserfolg",
		"answer":"failure"
	},
	{
		"question":"Familie",
		"answer":"family"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bauer",
		"answer":"farmer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fett",
		"answer":"fat"
	},
	{
		"question":"Feature",
		"answer":"feature"
	},
	{
		"question":"Feedback",
		"answer":"feedback"
	},
	{
		"question":"Feld",
		"answer":"field"
	},
	{
		"question":"Figur",
		"answer":"figure"
	},
	{
		"question":"Film",
		"answer":"film"
	},
	{
		"question":"Finden",
		"answer":"finding"
	},
	{
		"question":"Feuer",
		"answer":"fire"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fisch",
		"answer":"fish"
	},
	{
		"question":"Flug",
		"answer":"flight"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fokus",
		"answer":"focus"
	},
	{
		"question":"Essen",
		"answer":"food"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fußball",
		"answer":"football"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kraft",
		"answer":"force"
	},
	{
		"question":"Form",
		"answer":"form"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vermögen",
		"answer":"fortune"
	},
	{
		"question":"Stiftung",
		"answer":"foundation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Rahmen",
		"answer":"frame"
	},
	{
		"question":"Freiheit",
		"answer":"freedom"
	},
	{
		"question":"Freundschaft",
		"answer":"friendship"
	},
	{
		"question":"Spaß",
		"answer":"fun"
	},
	{
		"question":"Beerdigung",
		"answer":"funeral"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zukunft",
		"answer":"future"
	},
	{
		"question":"Spiel",
		"answer":"game"
	},
	{
		"question":"Müll",
		"answer":"garbage"
	},
	{
		"question":"Garten",
		"answer":"garden"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tor",
		"answer":"gate"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gen",
		"answer":"gene"
	},
	{
		"question":"Geschenk",
		"answer":"gift"
	},
	{
		"question":"Mädchen",
		"answer":"girl"
	},
	{
		"question":"Freundin",
		"answer":"girlfriend"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tor",
		"answer":"goal"
	},
	{
		"question":"Regierung",
		"answer":"government"
	},
	{
		"question":"Großmutter",
		"answer":"grandmother"
	},
	{
		"question":"Lebensmittelgeschäft",
		"answer":"grocery"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gruppe",
		"answer":"group"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wachstum",
		"answer":"growth"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gast",
		"answer":"guest"
	},
	{
		"question":"Anleitung",
		"answer":"guidance"
	},
	{
		"question":"Führer",
		"answer":"guide"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gitarre",
		"answer":"guitar"
	},
	{
		"question":"Haar",
		"answer":"hair"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hand",
		"answer":"hand"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hut",
		"answer":"hat"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kopf",
		"answer":"head"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gesundheit",
		"answer":"health"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hören",
		"answer":"hearing"
	},
	{
		"question":"Herz",
		"answer":"heart"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hitze",
		"answer":"heat"
	},
	{
		"question":"Höhe",
		"answer":"height"
	},
	{
		"question":"Autobahn",
		"answer":"highway"
	},
	{
		"question":"Historiker",
		"answer":"historian"
	},
	{
		"question":"Geschichte",
		"answer":"history"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zuhause",
		"answer":"home"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hausaufgaben",
		"answer":"homework"
	},
	{
		"question":"Honig",
		"answer":"honey"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hoffnung",
		"answer":"hope"
	},
	{
		"question":"Krankenhaus",
		"answer":"hospital"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hotel",
		"answer":"hotel"
	},
	{
		"question":"Haus",
		"answer":"house"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gehäuse",
		"answer":"housing"
	},
	{
		"question":"Eis",
		"answer":"ice"
	},
	{
		"question":"Idee",
		"answer":"idea"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bild",
		"answer":"image"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vorstellungskraft",
		"answer":"imagination"
	},
	{
		"question":"Einfluss",
		"answer":"impact"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bedeutung",
		"answer":"importance"
	},
	{
		"question":"Eindruck",
		"answer":"impression"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verbesserung",
		"answer":"improvement"
	},
	{
		"question":"Einkommen",
		"answer":"income"
	},
	{
		"question":"Unabhängigkeit",
		"answer":"independence"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hinweis",
		"answer":"indication"
	},
	{
		"question":"Industrie",
		"answer":"industry"
	},
	{
		"question":"Inflation",
		"answer":"inflation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Informationen",
		"answer":"information"
	},
	{
		"question":"Initiative",
		"answer":"initiative"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verletzung",
		"answer":"injury"
	},
	{
		"question":"Insekt",
		"answer":"insect"
	},
	{
		"question":"innen",
		"answer":"inside"
	},
	{
		"question":"Inspektion",
		"answer":"inspection"
	},
	{
		"question":"Inspektor",
		"answer":"inspector"
	},
	{
		"question":"Instanz",
		"answer":"instance"
	},
	{
		"question":"Anleitung",
		"answer":"instruction"
	},
	{
		"question":"Versicherung",
		"answer":"insurance"
	},
	{
		"question":"Absicht",
		"answer":"intention"
	},
	{
		"question":"Interaktion",
		"answer":"interaction"
	},
	{
		"question":"Interesse",
		"answer":"interest"
	},
	{
		"question":"Internet",
		"answer":"internet"
	},
	{
		"question":"Einführung",
		"answer":"introduction"
	},
	{
		"question":"Investition",
		"answer":"investment"
	},
	{
		"question":"Problem",
		"answer":"issue"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gegenstand",
		"answer":"item"
	},
	{
		"question":"Job",
		"answer":"job"
	},
	{
		"question":"Urteilsvermögen",
		"answer":"judgement"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schlüssel",
		"answer":"key"
	},
	{
		"question":"Art",
		"answer":"kind"
	},
	{
		"question":"König",
		"answer":"king"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wissen",
		"answer":"knowledge"
	},
	{
		"question":"Labor",
		"answer":"lab"
	},
	{
		"question":"Leiter",
		"answer":"ladder"
	},
	{
		"question":"Dame",
		"answer":"lady"
	},
	{
		"question":"See",
		"answer":"lake"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sprache",
		"answer":"language"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gesetz",
		"answer":"law"
	},
	{
		"question":"Führer",
		"answer":"leader"
	},
	{
		"question":"Führung",
		"answer":"leadership"
	},
	{
		"question":"Länge",
		"answer":"length"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ebene",
		"answer":"level"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bibliothek",
		"answer":"library"
	},
	{
		"question":"Leben",
		"answer":"life"
	},
	{
		"question":"Licht",
		"answer":"light"
	},
	{
		"question":"Linie",
		"answer":"line"
	},
	{
		"question":"Link",
		"answer":"link"
	},
	{
		"question":"Liste",
		"answer":"list"
	},
	{
		"question":"Literatur",
		"answer":"literature"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ort",
		"answer":"location"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verlust",
		"answer":"loss"
	},
	{
		"question":"Liebe",
		"answer":"love"
	},
	{
		"question":"Maschine",
		"answer":"machine"
	},
	{
		"question":"Magazin",
		"answer":"magazine"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wartung",
		"answer":"maintenance"
	},
	{
		"question":"Einkaufszentrum",
		"answer":"mall"
	},
	{
		"question":"Mann",
		"answer":"man"
	},
	{
		"question":"Management",
		"answer":"management"
	},
	{
		"question":"Manager",
		"answer":"manager"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hersteller",
		"answer":"manufacturer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Karte",
		"answer":"map"
	},
	{
		"question":"Markt",
		"answer":"market"
	},
	{
		"question":"Marketing",
		"answer":"marketing"
	},
	{
		"question":"Heirat",
		"answer":"marriage"
	},
	{
		"question":"Material",
		"answer":"material"
	},
	{
		"question":"Mathematik",
		"answer":"math"
	},
	{
		"question":"Angelegenheit",
		"answer":"matter"
	},
	{
		"question":"Mahlzeit",
		"answer":"meal"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bedeutung",
		"answer":"meaning"
	},
	{
		"question":"Messung",
		"answer":"measurement"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fleisch",
		"answer":"meat"
	},
	{
		"question":"Medien",
		"answer":"media"
	},
	{
		"question":"Medizin",
		"answer":"medicine"
	},
	{
		"question":"Medium",
		"answer":"medium"
	},
	{
		"question":"Mitglied",
		"answer":"member"
	},
	{
		"question":"Mitgliedschaft",
		"answer":"membership"
	},
	{
		"question":"Erinnerung",
		"answer":"memory"
	},
	{
		"question":"Menü",
		"answer":"menu"
	},
	{
		"question":"Nachricht",
		"answer":"message"
	},
	{
		"question":"Metall",
		"answer":"metal"
	},
	{
		"question":"Methode",
		"answer":"method"
	},
	{
		"question":"Mitternacht",
		"answer":"midnight"
	},
	{
		"question":"Geist",
		"answer":"mind"
	},
	{
		"question":"Mischung",
		"answer":"mixture"
	},
	{
		"question":"Modus",
		"answer":"mode"
	},
	{
		"question":"Modell",
		"answer":"model"
	},
	{
		"question":"Mama",
		"answer":"mom"
	},
	{
		"question":"Moment",
		"answer":"moment"
	},
	{
		"question":"Geld",
		"answer":"money"
	},
	{
		"question":"Monat",
		"answer":"month"
	},
	{
		"question":"Stimmung",
		"answer":"mood"
	},
	{
		"question":"Morgen",
		"answer":"morning"
	},
	{
		"question":"Maus",
		"answer":"mouse"
	},
	{
		"question":"Film",
		"answer":"movie"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schlamm",
		"answer":"mud"
	},
	{
		"question":"Musik",
		"answer":"music"
	},
	{
		"question":"Name",
		"answer":"name"
	},
	{
		"question":"Nation",
		"answer":"nation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Natur",
		"answer":"nature"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verhandlung",
		"answer":"negotiation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Netzwerk",
		"answer":"network"
	},
	{
		"question":"Nachrichten",
		"answer":"news"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zeitung",
		"answer":"newspaper"
	},
	{
		"question":"Nacht",
		"answer":"night"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hinweis",
		"answer":"note"
	},
	{
		"question":"nichts",
		"answer":"nothing"
	},
	{
		"question":"Nummer",
		"answer":"number"
	},
	{
		"question":"Objekt",
		"answer":"object"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verpflichtung",
		"answer":"obligation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Büro",
		"answer":"office"
	},
	{
		"question":"Öl",
		"answer":"oil"
	},
	{
		"question":"Betrieb",
		"answer":"operation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Meinung",
		"answer":"opinion"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gelegenheit",
		"answer":"opportunity"
	},
	{
		"question":"Orange",
		"answer":"orange"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ordnung",
		"answer":"order"
	},
	{
		"question":"Organisation",
		"answer":"organization"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ergebnis",
		"answer":"outcome"
	},
	{
		"question":"draußen",
		"answer":"outside"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ofen",
		"answer":"oven"
	},
	{
		"question":"Besitzer",
		"answer":"owner"
	},
	{
		"question":"Seite",
		"answer":"page"
	},
	{
		"question":"Farbe",
		"answer":"paint"
	},
	{
		"question":"Malerei",
		"answer":"painting"
	},
	{
		"question":"Papier",
		"answer":"paper"
	},
	{
		"question":"Teil",
		"answer":"part"
	},
	{
		"question":"Passagier",
		"answer":"passenger"
	},
	{
		"question":"Leidenschaft",
		"answer":"passion"
	},
	{
		"question":"Geduld",
		"answer":"patience"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zahlung",
		"answer":"payment"
	},
	{
		"question":"Strafe",
		"answer":"penalty"
	},
	{
		"question":"Menschen",
		"answer":"people"
	},
	{
		"question":"Prozentsatz",
		"answer":"percentage"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wahrnehmung",
		"answer":"perception"
	},
	{
		"question":"Leistung",
		"answer":"performance"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zeitraum",
		"answer":"period"
	},
	{
		"question":"Erlaubnis",
		"answer":"permission"
	},
	{
		"question":"Person",
		"answer":"person"
	},
	{
		"question":"Persönlichkeit",
		"answer":"personality"
	},
	{
		"question":"Perspektive",
		"answer":"perspective"
	},
	{
		"question":"Philosophie",
		"answer":"philosophy"
	},
	{
		"question":"Telefon",
		"answer":"phone"
	},
	{
		"question":"Foto",
		"answer":"photo"
	},
	{
		"question":"Physik",
		"answer":"physics"
	},
	{
		"question":"Klavier",
		"answer":"piano"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bild",
		"answer":"picture"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kuchen",
		"answer":"pie"
	},
	{
		"question":"Stück",
		"answer":"piece"
	},
	{
		"question":"Pizza",
		"answer":"pizza"
	},
	{
		"question":"Platz",
		"answer":"place"
	},
	{
		"question":"Plan",
		"answer":"plan"
	},
	{
		"question":"Plattform",
		"answer":"platform"
	},
	{
		"question":"Spieler",
		"answer":"player"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gedicht",
		"answer":"poem"
	},
	{
		"question":"Dichter",
		"answer":"poet"
	},
	{
		"question":"Poesie",
		"answer":"poetry"
	},
	{
		"question":"Punkt",
		"answer":"point"
	},
	{
		"question":"Polizei",
		"answer":"police"
	},
	{
		"question":"Politik",
		"answer":"policy"
	},
	{
		"question":"Politik",
		"answer":"politics"
	},
	{
		"question":"Umweltverschmutzung",
		"answer":"pollution"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bevölkerung",
		"answer":"population"
	},
	{
		"question":"Position",
		"answer":"position"
	},
	{
		"question":"Besitz",
		"answer":"possession"
	},
	{
		"question":"Möglichkeit",
		"answer":"possibility"
	},
	{
		"question":"Pfosten",
		"answer":"post"
	},
	{
		"question":"Topf",
		"answer":"pot"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kartoffel",
		"answer":"potato"
	},
	{
		"question":"Macht",
		"answer":"power"
	},
	{
		"question":"Praxis",
		"answer":"practice"
	},
	{
		"question":"Präferenz",
		"answer":"preference"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vorbereitung",
		"answer":"preparation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Präsenz",
		"answer":"presence"
	},
	{
		"question":"Präsentation",
		"answer":"presentation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Präsident",
		"answer":"president"
	},
	{
		"question":"Druck",
		"answer":"pressure"
	},
	{
		"question":"Preis",
		"answer":"price"
	},
	{
		"question":"Priorität",
		"answer":"priority"
	},
	{
		"question":"Problem",
		"answer":"problem"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verfahren",
		"answer":"procedure"
	},
	{
		"question":"Prozess",
		"answer":"process"
	},
	{
		"question":"Produkt",
		"answer":"product"
	},
	{
		"question":"Beruf",
		"answer":"profession"
	},
	{
		"question":"Professor",
		"answer":"professor"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gewinn",
		"answer":"profit"
	},
	{
		"question":"Programm",
		"answer":"program"
	},
	{
		"question":"Beförderung",
		"answer":"promotion"
	},
	{
		"question":"Eigentum",
		"answer":"property"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vorschlag",
		"answer":"proposal"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schutz",
		"answer":"protection"
	},
	{
		"question":"Psychologie",
		"answer":"psychology"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zweck",
		"answer":"purpose"
	},
	{
		"question":"Qualität",
		"answer":"quality"
	},
	{
		"question":"Quantität",
		"answer":"quantity"
	},
	{
		"question":"Königin",
		"answer":"queen"
	},
	{
		"question":"Frage",
		"answer":"question"
	},
	{
		"question":"Radio",
		"answer":"radio"
	},
	{
		"question":"Reichweite",
		"answer":"range"
	},
	{
		"question":"Rate",
		"answer":"rate"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verhältnis",
		"answer":"ratio"
	},
	{
		"question":"Reaktion",
		"answer":"reaction"
	},
	{
		"question":"Realität",
		"answer":"reality"
	},
	{
		"question":"Grund",
		"answer":"reason"
	},
	{
		"question":"Empfang",
		"answer":"reception"
	},
	{
		"question":"Rezept",
		"answer":"recipe"
	},
	{
		"question":"Anerkennung",
		"answer":"recognition"
	},
	{
		"question":"Empfehlung",
		"answer":"recommendation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Aufzeichnung",
		"answer":"record"
	},
	{
		"question":"Aufzeichnung",
		"answer":"recording"
	},
	{
		"question":"Reflexion",
		"answer":"reflection"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kühlschrank",
		"answer":"refrigerator"
	},
	{
		"question":"Region",
		"answer":"region"
	},
	{
		"question":"Beziehung",
		"answer":"relation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Beziehung",
		"answer":"relationship"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ersatz",
		"answer":"replacement"
	},
	{
		"question":"Republik",
		"answer":"republic"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ruf",
		"answer":"reputation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Anforderung",
		"answer":"requirement"
	},
	{
		"question":"Forschung",
		"answer":"research"
	},
	{
		"question":"Lösung",
		"answer":"resolution"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ressource",
		"answer":"resource"
	},
	{
		"question":"Antwort",
		"answer":"response"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verantwortung",
		"answer":"responsibility"
	},
	{
		"question":"Restaurant",
		"answer":"restaurant"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ergebnis",
		"answer":"result"
	},
	{
		"question":"Umsatz",
		"answer":"revenue"
	},
	{
		"question":"Überprüfung",
		"answer":"review"
	},
	{
		"question":"Revolution",
		"answer":"revolution"
	},
	{
		"question":"Risiko",
		"answer":"risk"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fluss",
		"answer":"river"
	},
	{
		"question":"Straße",
		"answer":"road"
	},
	{
		"question":"Rock",
		"answer":"rock"
	},
	{
		"question":"Rolle",
		"answer":"role"
	},
	{
		"question":"Raum",
		"answer":"room"
	},
	{
		"question":"Regel",
		"answer":"rule"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sicherheit",
		"answer":"safety"
	},
	{
		"question":"Salat",
		"answer":"salad"
	},
	{
		"question":"Salz",
		"answer":"salt"
	},
	{
		"question":"Probe",
		"answer":"sample"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zufriedenheit",
		"answer":"satisfaction"
	},
	{
		"question":"Skala",
		"answer":"scale"
	},
	{
		"question":"Szene",
		"answer":"scene"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schule",
		"answer":"school"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wissenschaft",
		"answer":"science"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bildschirm",
		"answer":"screen"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sekretär",
		"answer":"secretary"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bereich",
		"answer":"section"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sektor",
		"answer":"sector"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sicherheit",
		"answer":"security"
	},
	{
		"question":"Auswahl",
		"answer":"selection"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sinn",
		"answer":"sense"
	},
	{
		"question":"Serie",
		"answer":"series"
	},
	{
		"question":"Service",
		"answer":"service"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sitzung",
		"answer":"session"
	},
	{
		"question":"Einstellung",
		"answer":"setting"
	},
	{
		"question":"Form",
		"answer":"shape"
	},
	{
		"question":"Teilen",
		"answer":"share"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hemd",
		"answer":"shirt"
	},
	{
		"question":"Seite",
		"answer":"side"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zeichen",
		"answer":"sign"
	},
	{
		"question":"Unterschrift",
		"answer":"signature"
	},
	{
		"question":"Bedeutung",
		"answer":"significance"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sänger",
		"answer":"singer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Herr",
		"answer":"sir"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schwester",
		"answer":"sister"
	},
	{
		"question":"Standort",
		"answer":"site"
	},
	{
		"question":"Situation",
		"answer":"situation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Größe",
		"answer":"size"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fähigkeit",
		"answer":"skill"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gesellschaft",
		"answer":"society"
	},
	{
		"question":"Software",
		"answer":"software"
	},
	{
		"question":"Boden",
		"answer":"soil"
	},
	{
		"question":"Lösung",
		"answer":"solution"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sohn",
		"answer":"son"
	},
	{
		"question":"Lied",
		"answer":"song"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ton",
		"answer":"sound"
	},
	{
		"question":"Suppe",
		"answer":"soup"
	},
	{
		"question":"Quelle",
		"answer":"source"
	},
	{
		"question":"Raum",
		"answer":"space"
	},
	{
		"question":"Lautsprecher",
		"answer":"speaker"
	},
	{
		"question":"Rede",
		"answer":"speech"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sport",
		"answer":"sport"
	},
	{
		"question":"Quadrat",
		"answer":"square"
	},
	{
		"question":"Standard",
		"answer":"standard"
	},
	{
		"question":"Stern",
		"answer":"star"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zustand",
		"answer":"state"
	},
	{
		"question":"Aussage",
		"answer":"statement"
	},
	{
		"question":"Steak",
		"answer":"steak"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schritt",
		"answer":"step"
	},
	{
		"question":"Lager",
		"answer":"stock"
	},
	{
		"question":"Lagerung",
		"answer":"storage"
	},
	{
		"question":"Geschäft",
		"answer":"store"
	},
	{
		"question":"Geschichte",
		"answer":"story"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fremder",
		"answer":"stranger"
	},
	{
		"question":"Strategie",
		"answer":"strategy"
	},
	{
		"question":"Stress",
		"answer":"stress"
	},
	{
		"question":"Struktur",
		"answer":"structure"
	},
	{
		"question":"Student",
		"answer":"student"
	},
	{
		"question":"Studio",
		"answer":"studio"
	},
	{
		"question":"Studie",
		"answer":"study"
	},
	{
		"question":"Stil",
		"answer":"style"
	},
	{
		"question":"Thema",
		"answer":"subject"
	},
	{
		"question":"Erfolg",
		"answer":"success"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vorschlag",
		"answer":"suggestion"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sonne",
		"answer":"sun"
	},
	{
		"question":"Supermarkt",
		"answer":"supermarket"
	},
	{
		"question":"Chirurgie",
		"answer":"surgery"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sympathie",
		"answer":"sympathy"
	},
	{
		"question":"System",
		"answer":"system"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tisch",
		"answer":"table"
	},
	{
		"question":"Geschichte",
		"answer":"tale"
	},
	{
		"question":"Aufgabe",
		"answer":"task"
	},
	{
		"question":"Steuer",
		"answer":"tax"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tee",
		"answer":"tea"
	},
	{
		"question":"Lehrer",
		"answer":"teacher"
	},
	{
		"question":"Technologie",
		"answer":"technology"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fernsehen",
		"answer":"television"
	},
	{
		"question":"Temperatur",
		"answer":"temperature"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tennis",
		"answer":"tennis"
	},
	{
		"question":"Spannung",
		"answer":"tension"
	},
	{
		"question":"Begriff",
		"answer":"term"
	},
	{
		"question":"Test",
		"answer":"test"
	},
	{
		"question":"Dank",
		"answer":"thanks"
	},
	{
		"question":"Theorie",
		"answer":"theory"
	},
	{
		"question":"Sache",
		"answer":"thing"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gedanke",
		"answer":"thought"
	},
	{
		"question":"Kehle",
		"answer":"throat"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zeit",
		"answer":"time"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zunge",
		"answer":"tongue"
	},
	{
		"question":"Werkzeug",
		"answer":"tool"
	},
	{
		"question":"Zahn",
		"answer":"tooth"
	},
	{
		"question":"Top",
		"answer":"top"
	},
	{
		"question":"Thema",
		"answer":"topic"
	},
	{
		"question":"Stadt",
		"answer":"town"
	},
	{
		"question":"Handel",
		"answer":"trade"
	},
	{
		"question":"Tradition",
		"answer":"tradition"
	},
	{
		"question":"Trainer",
		"answer":"trainer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ausbildung",
		"answer":"training"
	},
	{
		"question":"Transport",
		"answer":"transportation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wahrheit",
		"answer":"truth"
	},
	{
		"question":"Typ",
		"answer":"type"
	},
	{
		"question":"Onkel",
		"answer":"uncle"
	},
	{
		"question":"Verständnis",
		"answer":"understanding"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gewerkschaft",
		"answer":"union"
	},
	{
		"question":"Einheit",
		"answer":"unit"
	},
	{
		"question":"Universität",
		"answer":"university"
	},
	{
		"question":"Benutzer",
		"answer":"user"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wert",
		"answer":"value"
	},
	{
		"question":"Variation",
		"answer":"variation"
	},
	{
		"question":"Vielfalt",
		"answer":"variety"
	},
	{
		"question":"Fahrzeug",
		"answer":"vehicle"
	},
	{
		"question":"Version",
		"answer":"version"
	},
	{
		"question":"Video",
		"answer":"video"
	},
	{
		"question":"Ansicht",
		"answer":"view"
	},
	{
		"question":"Dorf",
		"answer":"village"
	},
	{
		"question":"Virus",
		"answer":"virus"
	},
	{
		"question":"Stimme",
		"answer":"voice"
	},
	{
		"question":"Lautstärke",
		"answer":"volume"
	},
	{
		"question":"Krieg",
		"answer":"war"
	},
	{
		"question":"Warnung",
		"answer":"warning"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wasser",
		"answer":"water"
	},
	{
		"question":"Weg",
		"answer":"way"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schwäche",
		"answer":"weakness"
	},
	{
		"question":"Reichtum",
		"answer":"wealth"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wetter",
		"answer":"weather"
	},
	{
		"question":"Netz",
		"answer":"web"
	},
	{
		"question":"Hochzeit",
		"answer":"wedding"
	},
	{
		"question":"Woche",
		"answer":"week"
	},
	{
		"question":"während",
		"answer":"while"
	},
	{
		"question":"Frau",
		"answer":"wife"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wind",
		"answer":"wind"
	},
	{
		"question":"Flügel",
		"answer":"wing"
	},
	{
		"question":"Gewinner",
		"answer":"winner"
	},
	{
		"question":"Frau",
		"answer":"woman"
	},
	{
		"question":"Holz",
		"answer":"wood"
	},
	{
		"question":"Wort",
		"answer":"word"
	},
	{
		"question":"Arbeit",
		"answer":"work"
	},
	{
		"question":"Arbeiter",
		"answer":"worker"
	},
	{
		"question":"Welt",
		"answer":"world"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schriftsteller",
		"answer":"writer"
	},
	{
		"question":"Schreiben",
		"answer":"writing"
	},
	{
		"question":"Jahr",
		"answer":"year"
	},
	{
		"question":"Jugend",
		"answer":"youth"
	}
]